One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
the tides of time, and humanity's dreams...
They cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek freedom,
these things will never cease to be.
I only believe in the future -- I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
I don't really need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Landfall in Alabasta
Nanohana
Kingdom of Alabasta
So this is one of Alabasta's cities?
Food!
Listen, guys!
Practice self-control
instead of acting on instinct!
Yes, Nami!
The guy who most needed
to hear that is already gone.
Food place!
Get back here!
Nothing but instinct.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Find the biggest commotion,
and he'll be there.
Bingo.
Ugh! He needs to be more aware
of that bounty on his head,
especially in a big country like this!
Don't worry about him.
Let's just eat first.
We'll strategize more after that.
They're all the same...
What's wrong?
Mr. 3's ship!
That creep didn't kick
the bucket after all?!
No mistaking it!
His ship runs on the power
of his Wax-Wax Fruit!
The bastard's here?
This is bad.
Food pla-a-a-a-a-ace!
What's that? There's
a weird smell in the air!
Oh! Found it! A food place!
So? What do you want from me?
To let me capture you quietly.
Sorry. No can do.
Yeah, I figured.
I'm in the middle
of locating another pirate.
Cards on the table,
I'm not here for your head.
So look the other way.
No can do.
See, I'm a Marine...
and you're a pirate.
What a silly reason.
Let's have some fun then.
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
A food place! I finally found one!
Time to eat! I'm starving!
Old guy! Food! Food! Food!
On the double!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Food! Food! Food!
Wow!
These are beautiful!
On the Outskirts
of Nanohana
I love these kinds of clothes!
While I realize I asked you
to shop for us, Sanji,
aren't these outfits for dancer girls?
And they look amazing on you!
I asked for ordinary civilian clothes...
Dancers are civilians too!
But we have to cross a desert...
Don't worry!
If you get tired, I'll carry you!
Truly a lost cause.
But, compared to them, you guys
look like a couple of bandits.
What, and you don't?
Chopper!
What are you doing?
It reeks.
That reminds me, where did you go?
Various places!
Is he feeling ill?
Oh, the perfume's getting to him.
Perfume?
Oh, right! Tony has a sensitive nose!
– Oh, this...
– They are often very potent.
Like this?
Ahh! Stop!
My love greatly deepens, Mellorine!
You always this idiotic?
Huh?!
In any case, we've accomplished
our first goal of gathering supplies!
Yes...
We're going to a place
called Yuba, was it?
That's right, but going there
means crossing the desert.
So good! The food here is tasty!
Y-Yeah. Thanks. But...
Well, you... ought to
scram while you can.
How come?
Why, you...!
Who the hell did this?!
What the hell?!
What's the big idea?!
Oh! Apologies
for disturbing your meal!
What idiot would do
something this crazy?!
Lu...!
Hey! Luf–
Straw Hat!
I've been looking for you, Straw Hat!
So you actually came to Alabasta!
Stop eating!
Isn't he...?
I'm Marine Captain Smoker.
I'm in charge of Loguetown.
You're that smoke guy!
What are you doing here?!
Why you...!
Hold it!
Thanks for the meal!
Huh?
Hold it!
Wait, Luffy! It's me!
Hey! Wait up! Hey! Luffy!
They didn't pay...
This is bad! My Gum-Gum moves
don't work on that guy at all!
Gotta just run for now!
Tashigi!
Y-Yes, Captain Smoker?!
Do you need a towel?
This place sure is hot!
Get him! It's Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?!
I'll stop him!
Tashigi! Round up the Marines!
Search every nook and cranny
for Straw Hat's crew!
Yes, sir!
People with powers are fighting!
Whoa!
Straw Hat's crew! That means...
Roronoa Zoro is in this city!
White Snake!
Where could Luffy have gone?
Honestly! It's as if our
captain needs a babysitter!
Oh! Nami!
Hey, now! This is bad!
Big trouble's brewing
if we don't make tracks soon.
Big trouble?
The Marines are here.
The Marines?!
The sooner we find Luffy,
the sooner we leave town!
Hey! Hide!
– What for?!
– What is it?!
The Marines!
There seems to be a big commotion!
Don't let him escape! After him!
Some idiot pirate must be
running around town or something.
Get back here, Straw Hat!
– It was you?!
Hey, Zoro!
Oh?! So that's where everyone is?!
You idiot! Ditch those guys first!
It's the Straw Hat crew! Over there!
Okay, so... what now?
– We run, obviously!
– Hurry! To the ship!
What are you doing?! Let's get back!
Hey, you!
Stop! Don't let them escape!
Fall back!
Captain!
Straw Hat is mine!
Wh-Whoa! Here he comes!
White Blow!
You're mine!
Heat Haze!
You, huh?
Give it up.
You may be smoke,
but I'm fire.
We're too evenly matched
to settle things between us.
He has devil fruit powers?!
Who is he, anyway?!
Ace?!
You haven't changed a bit, Luffy.
Ace?! Is that you, Ace?!
You ate a devil fruit?!
Yep! The Flame-Flame Fruit!
Captain Smoker!
Securing the perimeter!
No time to chat!
Get moving! I'll catch up!
Leave them to me!
– Go!
– Let's go!
Y-Yeah!
But, Luffy!
Who is that guy?!
White...
Spark!
Wh-What is that?!
A house fire?
No, that's no ordinary fire!
What in the world is happening?
It's a fight between
flame and smoke?!
He did say he ate
the Flame-Flame Fruit.
But, Luffy! Is that guy really
your older brother?
Yup! His name's Ace!
That you have a brother
isn't what's surprising.
Why would he be in the Grand Line?
Ace is a pirate.
He left our island three years
before me to look for One Piece.
– What?!
A-Anyway, let's hurry
back to the ship!
Run before they catch up!
Yes, Nami!
Still, I never thought
I'd see Ace in a place like this!
The path splits here!
Go left, Usopp! Everyone catch that?!
Yes! I'll follow Nami
wherever she goes!
Enough, pervy cook!
So cool! The fireball's
even higher now!
A battle of flame and smoke
really is endless.
But we already knew that.
Where did the Straw Hats go?
They're gone!
So is Ace! We've lost sight of him!
I finally caught up to Straw Hat
in the Grand Line,
but Portgas D. Ace
just had to get in the way.
Hurry and load the supplies!
We're leaving right away!
Hurry!
Unfurl the sails!
Say... We just got to the island,
but are we already leaving?
Yes. This town was only a stopover
for some needed supplies.
Next, we sail the ship up the river
farther into Alabasta.
Our next destination is Erumalu,
the City of Green.
Erumalu?
Hurry!
Pick up the pace!
All set!
Okay! Let's set sail!
Huh?
Y'know...
I get the feeling
we're missing someone...
Huh?!
That's weird.
Where did they go?
Man! I guess my letting you escape
was pretty much pointless.
Hey!
Ace!
Been a while, Luffy.
Right back at you, Ace!
How many years has it been?
Good question.
But Luffy, I see you still
do things at your own pace,
just like when we were kids.
You too, Ace!
I'm surprised you ate a devil fruit,
but besides that, you're the same!
Like when you'd sneak into
the fields, eat 100 watermelons,
and then spit the seeds out
like a gun and run!
That wasn't me! That was you!
Yeah, and they
whupped you good for it!
Again, that was you!
I only watched and laughed!
So we didn't change!
Nope!
Brings back memories!
So...
weren't your friends
looking for you?
Yeah.
But, Ace. What are you
doing in this country?
Huh?
You mean, you didn't get
the message I left back in Drum?
Drum?
Yeah. Don't sweat it,
though. No biggie.
I'm in these waters seeing
to a minor business matter,
so I thought I might look you up.
Minor business?
I joined up with
the Whitebeard Pirates.
Whitebeard Pirates?
Here's the mark
of a Whitebeard Pirate.
It's my pride.
Oh?
So, Luffy, how 'bout joining
Whitebeard's crew?
Your friends can come too.
No.
Oh well, just thought I'd ask.
Whitebeard is the greatest pirate
I've ever known.
I'm gonna help him
become King of the Pirates...
It won't be you, Luffy.
That's fine! Then I guess
we gotta fight!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates.
Hey! Don't drink it all, Luffy!
Something big happening in town?
Smoker and all his men
left the ship.
But... this is perfect!
Here's my chance to try and escape!
Mr. 11.
Full
Fledged
You know my codename, so you
must be members of Baroque Works!
Millions, I take it?
Hurry and untie me!
Full
Fledged
Indeed, we are members
of Baroque Works.
We're billions, though.
We're next to become number agents.
Full
Fledged
Mr. 11, you're barely an agent, seeing
as you're not much stronger than us.
O-Oh! I see!
My mistake, billions.
But could you hurry and untie me?
That'd be stupid of us!
Full
Fledged
With you gone, one of us will get
promoted to a number agent.
So let's empty
one of the agents' seats!
W-Wait!
Hey!
Fire Fist Ace is in this town!
What?!
Full
Fledged
Fire Fist Ace?!
The Second Division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates?
If we can take down Ace,
we're guaranteed to be number agents!
I-Is it really okay
to set sail without Luffy?
The Marines will be
all over the harbors.
We need to hide the ship first.
There should be a cove ahead
that's hidden from view!
So we'll wait for things
to cool down, then look for Luffy.
Geez! He's always, always,
causing trouble like this!
He's a real reliable captain...
Oh! The ocean!
See your ship?
End of the line!
Oh!
There it is!
Hey! Over here! Guys!
Hey, Luffy. Go on ahe–
Never mind.
Oh! There he is! It's Luffy!
I found Luffy!
Where is he?
Yeah. That's definitely his dumb mug.
Huh?!
I'm back!
Sanji! Tony!
Oh, come on!
Not again.
Sorry about that, Sanji and Chopper.
How do you never learn from any
of this?! I oughta just gut you here!
Yeah! Do you even realize
the trouble you've caused?!
Try to act somewhat like a captain!
Sorry.
Oh, that's right! Ace!
Ace?
Your brother was with you?
Is it okay to just leave him there?
Oh, it's okay! Ace is pretty strong!
He's strong?
Yup. Back in the day he hadn't
eaten the Flame-Flame Fruit,
but I still never beat him
in a single fight!
Ace is that strong!
There's a flesh-and-blood person
you could never beat?!
So the monster's big bro
is an even bigger monster.
That's right! I lost to him all the time!
But now, I'd beat him good!
Guessing you've got
nothing to base that on.
Who...
can beat who now?!
Oh! Ace! These are
the friends we talked about!
Oh! Thank you all for looking
after my kid brother.
– Huh? Oh, not at all.
And maybe he's sometimes
a bit too much to handle, but...
– No, not at all.
Take good care of him.
Well, you two
probably want to catch up.
Come on in.
I'll make some tea.
No, that's okay. Don't trouble
yourself on my account.
T-Talk about unexpected...
That's for sure.
I'd have thought he'd be
as reckless as Luffy.
There's no way this
sensible man is Luffy's brother!
He's nice and he cares
about his kid brother.
Brothers can be so wonderful!
The sea is just full of surprises.
Come now, everyone!
See! Aren't these guys neat?!
Baroque Works!
Those are the billions' ships!
Fire Fist Ace and Straw Hat Luffy!
Don't think you've gotten away!
We'll show you just what
Baroque Works' billions are made of!
Those guys again?
Luffy. I'll take out the trash.
What's he going to do?
Especially in that little boat...
Let's see the Whitebeard Pirates'
Second Division commander in action.
Here he comes! Fire Fist Ace!
Just try us, hotshot,
but it's you against five ships!
He jumped!
F-Fire!
Blast him into a watery grave!
Fire Fist!
Woo-hoo!
A-Amazing!
Captain Smoker!
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew
are nowhere to be found.
What do you make of this, Tashigi?
Vivi was with them.
Vivi? Princess Nefertari Vivi
was with the Straw Hats?
She must be a hostage.
The princess' abduction
must be part of some plot.
No. Vivi was acting like
she was part of their crew.
The princess? Part of their crew?
There's something
afoot in this country.
Captain Smoker!
I'm sorry, sir!
Mr. 11 was done in by someone
while tied up on the ship!
We still haven't located
the Straw Hats, either!
Get it together. I believe
I know where they're headed.
He's gunning for Crocodile.
Crocodile?!
A pirate backed by the government,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
You know I hate
the Seven Warlords, right?
Especially that detestable man.
B-But he's currently an ally
to the Marines and the government!
He's always been clever, that pirate.
He's not the type to roll over
and beg for the government. Not him!
Tashigi! Remember this one thing!
A pirate's a pirate,
no matter his status!
If we head toward Crocodile,
we'll find Straw Hat.
It'll all come to light
when we get there.
And next time, you won't
get away, Straw Hat!
Yoo-hoo!
Ace is one of us now!
Cheers!
Whad'ya mean, I'm one of you?
Here's to delicious drinks!
Cheers!
Pay it no mind!
Here's to delicious drinks!
They'll find any excuse
to have a drink!
Cheers!
Here's to delicious drinks!
Medicine is gross!
Ace! Are you sure you won't join us?
I'm chasing a certain man.
His name's Blackbeard.
Blackbeard?
He's the pirate who attacked
the Kingdom of Drum!
He once belonged
to Whitebeard's Second Division,
one of my own men.
But he committed the most
grievous act any pirate could.
He killed a crewmate
and jumped ship.
Since I'm the commander,
I gotta take responsibility for him.
So that's why you're
chasing after him?
We've just started up
the Sandora River.
First, we'll land at Erumalu.
We'll then head into Alabasta's
interior to reach Yuba here!
That's where we'll find
the leader of the Rebellion.
I see. Yuba it is then.
I'll follow Nami and Vivi
wherever they go!
Drop dead, Love Cook.
Say what?! You–
A-Anyways! It seems we'll be
traveling together for a bit!
Yeah, yeah! His brother is
more than welcome here!
Let's have some fun, Ace!
– Yeah!